It's started! 161 hearts on YouTube!
Yay!
So, this time, we are going to present you with these five members.
Let's introduce ourselves from this side.
I'm Kyushu Abun and I'm 16 years old.
I'm Ichi.
How old are you?
I am 18 years old.
Yes, I'm 19, I'm Runa Izuka.
I'm 16, I'm Mie Fujiseki.
I'm 17, I'm Shin Harai.
I know we may be an unusual five, but...
What we're going to try this time is
The earphone gun game!
Have you ever been to YouTube?
Yes, I have!
Maybe it sounds like YouTube to you.
Aren't you excited?
Subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel.
What do you think? We're five loud guys.
Who's confident?
About Amuku?
Well, yes.
Yes, you do.
It sounds so easy, doesn't it?
Yes, it is.
You can gesture, right?
Yes, I am.
For now.
I'm just saying.
If it were easy, there would be no more gestures.
That's what I'm saying.
That's how we're going to do it.
Yes, sir.
What do you mean by "supplementary explanation"?Supplementary explanation means...
Oh, what is it? I'm scared.
If you fail, you'll be punished for it at the next release event.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean?
What?
I'll tell you what's going on.
We'll play five rounds.
If you succeed three times, you get a penalty.
Three times?
No, that's too many.
Three times for five players?
No, you can do it.
We'll do it right in front of the fans.
Oh, you mean, not just one, but all of us?
Is that what you mean?
The whole group.
Punishment game.
The four guys after the fans don't have to do anything.
Just the five of us?
That's what I mean.
I don't get it.
Then why don't we just avoid the penalty game?
You're right.
Let's try one at a time, one at a time.
If it's too easy, we'll stop.
That's right.
If there's a gesture, it's too easy.
Don't go in too hard yourself.
Wouldn't it be cool to avoid the penalty?
Sure would be.
That's so cool.
I'm going for it.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
We're all in this together.
Let's avoid the penalty.
Let's do our best!
Nakamura Kaito's vocal cords for PIT PIT!
Do you want to do it after that?
I'll do the top one.
Shut up!
I'll do it.
All right.
Who wants to do the second one?
Okay, I'll do it.
What about number three?
Oh, great.
And the fourth?
Yay!
I think I picked a good one.
That's good.
I picked a good one.
Okay, so the last one is good.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
I'm off.
I don't know if I can remember this.
One tablespoon of sugar.
Salt and mushrooms.
Salt and pepper.
pepper
A pinch of salt and pepper
1 tablespoon sugar
OK!
OK! That's what I'm talking about.Oh! What the hell is this?
Sugar.
Sugar, sugar, sugar
Wow!
Sugar mmm
Squeeze sugar
Tablespoon
Tbsp sugar
tablespoon
Tablespoon
1?
Are you sure it's 1?
You said one, right?
One.
One tablespoon of sugar.
Whoa!
I'm not done.
Salt.
Salt
and
Ha ha ha
pepper
eh?
Pepper
pepper
Salt and...
Salt and pepper
A little.
a little, a little
a little bit
Eh, 1 tablespoon sugarEh, 1 tablespoon sugar
A pinch of salt and pepper
ohhhh!
I've got it, I've got it, I've got it, I've got it, I've got it
oh oh oh
sugar
Sugar.
huh?
Oh, sweet, sweet
Sugar sugar
Yes, sugar
Tablespoon
And still more
1 tablespoon sugar
Salt and
Pepper
pepper
a little
A little
Oh, great.
Huh?
A tablespoon of sugar
A pinch of salt and pepper
1 tablespoon sugar
A pinch of salt and pepper.
Oh!
wow!
sugarsugar
ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Why?
A-ha-ha
sugar
tablespoon
Tablespoon
Salt and
6 fl. oz.
A-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha
Salt and
ah ha ha ha ha
salt
and
pepper
is ?
Pepper
pepper
A little.
a little
sugar
tbsp.tablespoon
Tablespoon
Salt and
Salt
Pepper
pepper
a little
Aah!
1 tablespoon of sugar and a pinch of salt and pepper
Eh, the correct answer is
1 tablespoon sugar
A pinch of salt and pepper.
Am I right?
This is...
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
I got it! I got it!
I got it!
There it is!
Oh, my God.
I'm in.
That was great.
It's okay. It's okay.
I got it. I got it.
I shivered.
I shuddered.
That was really great.
What's that?
The blue one's the worst.
Let's see.let's see
The biggest problem
The biggest problem.
It's easier with gestures.
That's easy.
When you say "one"...
That's a lot.
I know what you mean.
You're right.
It's a gesture.
It's easy to understand.
Shall we go without gestures then?
That was a service.
That's right.
The top one.
That's for sure.
Kaito Miyachika, singer
Kanya Yoshizawa Singing
Kaito Matsukura Sings
Kaito Miyachika Sings
Kaito Matsuda Sings
Kaito Miyachika Singing
Ukisho In Tokyo
Ukisho, in Tokyo
Ukisho, in Tokyo, getting lost
Ukisho Lost in Tokyo
Ukisho, lost in Tokyo
Ukisho I worked part-time
Ukisho, lost
Lost in Tokyo
Ukisho, laughing!
Great!
Lost in the water. Lost in the water.Ukisho, lost, lost
Ukisho, good luck. Maribo.
Ukisho Laughing
Lost in Tokyo
Lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo
Laughing at the floating place
Laughing in Tokyo
in Tokyo
Lost in Tokyo
Lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo, lost in Tokyo
Ukisho, Japanese style
Laughing
Ukisho, Tokyo.
Here!
Tokyo!
Here?
Where is this?
Here!
Tokyo.
and
Tokyo
in Tokyo
Lost in
Tokyo Dome
Shinken
Baka
In Tokyo
10 seconds ago
Lost!Lost!
Lost!
Lost in Tokyo!
Lost in Tokyo. Tokyo!
Okay, let's go next.
Tokyo Dome.
Tokyo Dome
Do!
What?
Tokyo Dome
Tokyo Dome.
Tokyo Dome?
Let's go!
End!
Answers, please.
Tokyo Dome
Tokyo
In Tokyo
Lost and groggy
Lost, lost, lost...
It's not the same thing at all!
I'm lost.
Lost.
I made it too loud. I don't know what I'm saying.
Then it's a failure.
Fail.
What else? But if I fail twice more, it's a penalty game.
That's true.
There's still room.
There's room for more.
Oh, my God. It's so hard.
It's so hard!
Tokyo DomeTokyo Dome
Tokyo Dome
Oh, I gave it to you.
Tokyo is a pin!
No, it's not!
To this store.
Coco Business
Dashimaki is
This is where the business begins.
Do you have Dashimaki in this store?
Conbini! Convenience store!
Dashimaki!
Tamparin!
Do you have any oshimaki in this store?
What?
Do you have any tashimaki here?
Yes, you're done.
Here.
Here?
In the center of town
The whole town?
I can see that.
Here!
Here.
Convenience store!
Convenience store?
Bugs...
Bugs.
Insects?
Bugs!
Mushi!
Bugs.Bugs.
I got one!
Bought!
Yes, it's over!
Ahhh~!
Sorry, sorry.
of this place
Here
Convenience store.
Convenience?
Convenience store!
Convenience store.
Worms.
Bugs.
I got bugs!
Here at the convenience store
I bought bugs at this convenience store!
I bought a bug at this convenience store!
Wow!
At this convenience store
I bought a bug at this convenience store!
I'm sorry, I really don't know.
Here.
Reverse Lo...
of here!
of!
At the convenience store
Convenience store
I bought a bug.
I'll get some too.
How to let us know
insects
inun-
(after the -masu stem of a verb) the moment that ...
I bought a
It's amazing.
Here at the convenience store
I bought a bug.
Really?
Right here at this convenience store.
I bought some bugs at this convenience store.
Do you have any left overs in this store?
Laughs
Wait a minute.
That was disgusting.
It was so hard!
Failed.
One more to go.
I'll do the penalty game.
Two more rounds, and you're good to go.
Certainly.
Ending
Yes, I was warned for chewing chewing gum in class
I can't do it.
Ukisho?
Ukisho... No, no... 32
Ukisho, no.
Ukisho, let's go.
Here.
All the way.
Okay.
Tsukane Ukisho.
steeds
UTSUSHO SEGASUSU
simples
Okay.
Ah!Uh...
I couldn't do it.
It's crazy.
Floater, 16.
Floating place, but criticizing.
Floater, follow me.
Ukisho, front desk
Floating place, it's hard to do
floating place
floating place, why?
I was warned.
Oh, wow.
I'm in class.
Tokyo
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Jyu, Jyu, Jyu, Jyu, Jyu-don
Slowly, slowly, slowly
Lesson
10, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15, 15
class
During class
in class
at 2
at
Watermelon
I ate it.
Just, just got a warning
I just snapped in the middle
in the middle
Ha-ha-ha
I was warned
Cautioned
milk
Attention.Attention.
Yes, so it's over!
at the end of the week
In class
During class
I ate a watermelon.
Yuka?
Watermelon
I ate a watermelon
I ate
I ate it.
I ate it because
for a long time
cloth
story
I'm sleepy
One more time, one more time, one more time
In class
Because I ate a watermelon
Animals table
I'm sleepy.
Sleepy
JUMPLE
I've lost everything.
What?
I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy.got to be
Got it.
In class
I ate a watermelon.
Because I ate it.
I got sleepy
I got sleepy.
In class.
Oh, yeah.
During class.
During class
Watermelon.
Because I ate it
I ate it.
I got sleepy.
I feel sleepy
Debut
Sleepy
Yes, I'm done
In class
I made my debut.
OK, I'm done.
During class.
I ate watermelon
I made my debut.
What is it?
What's on it?
I was in class.
Chewing gum during class.
I got a warning.I've been warned.
Wait a minute.
What does it say?
It's just a bunch of tut-tutting. I can't understand a word of it.
It's hard!
I'll just say it's harder than I thought.
Next time, it's hard.
Failed.
Aaaaahhh!
Oops.
Uh-oh.
Hold on.
Let's do the inch one more time.
Just in case.
You're right.
I've never done 3 inches before.
Good luck, everyone.
If you succeed, you'll avoid the penalty game.
Oh! You did it!
Thank you so much for this.
This is really, really good.
Thank you so much.
This is how I'm getting to thank you.
The evaluation of Haruma Sasahara's expression is 100 threads
It's the hardest! This is the hardest! It's the last one!
Thank you for watching!
Sasahara
Sekihara
Haruma
of
Today
NORIMA
ThreadingThreading
Yarn Sweets
threading
I get it.
Haruma Sasahara's
NORIMAHA
Threading
100 threads
Today's
Nuruma is
100 threads
Are you sure?
Sasahara
Haruma.
Today
Haruma Sasahara's
Nuruma is
Threading
Haruma Sasahara's
Nuruma is
Haruma Sasahara's today's Nuruma is 100 threads
100 threads
The end
Go, go, go, go
Sasahara Haruma's
Today's
Haruma Sasahara's
Today
Nuruma is
ThreadingThreading
threading
Thousand
Haruma Sasahara's
Haruma Sasahara's today's Noruma is
100 threads
Not yet.
Haruma Sasahara's
Today's Noruma is
100 threads
Here it comes!
Haruma Sasahara
of
Today's NORUMA
Today's
Muscle Co.
Haruma Sasahara's
Today's
Nuruma is
Today
Nuruma
Nuruma is
Threading
100 threads
100 threadsOne hundred.
Wow!
The end.
Here it comes, here it comes
Haruma Sasahara's
Today's Noruma is
100 threads
Haruma Sasahara's
Today's Noruma threaded 100 threads
Wow!
Yay!
Yes!
I played a deciding role in the production!
That was fun!
I'm so tired!
How was it? Miyuka!
So hot!
It was fun!
It was hard!
How about you, Isshi?
I don't remember anymore.
I don't remember the first problem.
That's true.
It was pretty loose at first.
But it got harder and harder.
It was a lot of fun.
And I thought we had a bonding experience.
How do you feel about the trampoline bonding?
I don't know. It's not going to stop me from bonding with him.
It's not gonna last.
It's not gonna stay, is it?
We have to take it to a higher and higher level.We need to raise the bar higher and higher.
I see.
The next day, you won't be able to stay up much longer.
So, this time
I'd say it was a great success.
How was it? Yes!
Yay!
What's next?
See you next week!
I'll protect you.
Shut up!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the hell?
He's proposing.
I'll marry you.
Pose for a change.
Wait a minute, that's pretty hard.